Hey everyone, welcome Back to the channel.05
did you know the average human brain can generate enough electricity
to power a light bulb?
00:10 Seriously, like a tiny little light
bulb inside your head. 00:15 I know,
right? Mind blowing.
00:20 this amazing biological marvel is
constantly processing information, forming memories,
and controlling your every movement.
00:25 It's a supercomputer.
00:30 so next time you feel overwhelmed,
remember that your brain is truly an incredible machine.
00:35 and for today's video, that is
all the time we have. 00:40 I hope
you guys enjoyed today's little educational nugget.
Make sure to give this video a thumbs up. Subscribe to the
channel for more mind blowing facts.
00:45 Hit that notification Bell so
you never miss a new upload.
00:50 and as always, thanks for watching.