Hey everyone. Welcome back to the channel 00
intro. I'm your host Alex and
today we're diving deep into the animal kingdom.
005 fact 1 Did you know the
African elephant can lift a car? Yes,
you heard that right. 00:10 Fact 2
the world's fastest land animal is the cheetah,
clocking speeds over 70 miles per hour.
00:15 Fact 3 and the smallest primate,
the pygmy marmoset, is so tiny you could fit
one in your hand. 00:20 fact 4
the giant squid has a mind blowing massive eye that's
bigger than a dinner plate. 00:25 Fact
5 Did you know that some species of fish can survive out
of water for extended periods?
Fascinating. 00:30 outro these are
just a few of the incredible facts out there.
Subscribe for more amazing animal wonders. And don't
forget to hit that notification bell.
00:35 Outro music fades Animals
Amazing facts. Nature,
wildlife,